export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt : "Which is not considered a common method of transmission for HIV?",
        optionA:"blood",
        optionB:"genital secretions",
        optionC:"breast milk",
        optionD:"urine",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt : "About one-fourth of all people with HIV/AIDS areâ€¦",
        optionA:"homosexual men",
        optionB:"living in southern U.S. states",
        optionC:"over the age of 50",
        optionD:"bisexual women",
        answer:"C"
    },
    {
        prompt : "What does it mean to be HIV-positive?",
        optionA:"It means that you have AIDS.",
        optionB:"It means that two tests have been identified positive for HIV.",
        optionC:"the means the virus cannot be passed to another person",
        optionD:"none of the above",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt : "Where did HIV originate?",
        optionA:"A chimpanzee",
        optionB:"Mad cow disease",
        optionC:"A strain of the hepatitis virus",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        prompt : "What is AIDS?",
        optionA:"A fungal infection",
        optionB:"A rare blood cancer caused by HIV",
        optionC:"A group of diseases caused by HIV",
        optionD:"The final stage of HIV",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt : "what are T cells ?",
        optionA:"T cells are a type of white blood cell",
        optionB:"T cells scan cells for abnormalities",
        optionC:"T cells coordinate immune responses",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt : "how does HIV becomes AIDS ?",
        optionA:"HIV attacks the T cells",
        optionB:"HIV makes multiple copies of itself",
        optionC:"HIV destroys cells in the body",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt : "How many stages are there in HIV infection",
        optionA:"One",
        optionB:"Two",
        optionC:"Three",
        optionD:"Four",
        answer:"C"
    },
    {
        prompt : "When did the world health organization first proposed a definition for AIDS ?",
        optionA:"1950",
        optionB:"1986",
        optionC:"1965",
        optionD:"1976",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt : "Which is the second most common way of spreading HIV ?",
        optionA:"Sexual intercourse with HIV infected",
        optionB:"Sharing needles",
        optionC:"Sharing food",
        optionD:"From infected mother to child",
        answer:"B"
    }
]